<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Lansin&#39;s blog</title>
        <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/</link>
        <description>Life is all about experience, adventure, and joy.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>lanhsin369@outlook.com (Lanhsin)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>lanhsin369@outlook.com (Lanhsin)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:47:30 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Make Blogging Great Again</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 23:19:27 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/blog.jpeg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>I&rsquo;ve wanted to start a blog for a long time, my own little space on the internet where I can just be myself. But it&rsquo;s more than that. Blogging is like creating your own digital identity, a place where you are not controlled by tricky social media rules.
In the following section, I will try my best to persuade you to join me in this blogging journey.
Discovering Meaning in Sharing You know, there&rsquo;s this idea that many of us live by, something like, &ldquo;If you don&rsquo;t capture it, it&rsquo;s as if you&rsquo;ve never been there; if you don&rsquo;t tag it, it&rsquo;s as if you&rsquo;ve never seen, played, or read it; if you don&rsquo;t share it, it&rsquo;s as if you&rsquo;ve never done it.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Interview Notes</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/game/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:47:30 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/game/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/Interview.jpeg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>I had my second interview last Thursday. It provided me a valuable opportunity to sharpen my interview skills. The mix of excitement and nervousness was evident, but overall, this experience was better than my first interview. I succeeded in lightening the mood. I noticed positive interactions as they frequently nodded in agreement and took notes during our discussion.
Questions I Was Asked: Self-introduction Why this country? Why choose this program? Why this industry?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Seeking Purpose: Reflections on &#39;Why&#39;</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/fifth_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 14:19:27 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/fifth_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Recently, I read some articles by Simon Sinek, recommended by my mentor. My mentor encouraged me to discover my personal &ldquo;Why Statement.&rdquo; This concept, introduced by Sinek, emphasizes the driving force behind our actions, our motivations, and our ultimate goals. In essence, it&rsquo;s our calling, our mission, to which we would willingly dedicate our lives.
My mentor&rsquo;s &ldquo;Why Statement&rdquo; was deeply inspiring. Her aspiration is to inspire and empower young individuals, fostering positive change in them, and, over time, in the world at large.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Three Days Without My Laptop</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/fouth_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 21:51:50 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/fouth_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Three days ago, my laptop, which I&rsquo;ve used faithfully for nearly six years, ran into technical issues. Upon starting it up, I was met with the message:
&ldquo;To interrupt normal startup, press enter.&rdquo;
Given my affinity for technology, I saw this as an opportunity to delve deeper into the workings of my laptop.
After some independent research, I discovered others had faced similar issues. Their solution was to access the BIOS system, adjust the optimized defaults, and then restart.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Deloitte Virtual Risk Analysis Project</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/second_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:19:27 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/second_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/deloitte.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Enrolling in Forge&rsquo;s Virtual Program was driven by my passion to delve deep into the intricacies of data analysis, especially within the context of real-world applications. The program provided a platform to not only refine my analytical skills but also understand the tangible impact data-driven insights can have on businesses.
Throughout this journey, I acquired a holistic perspective on data processing, from sourcing and cleaning data to deriving actionable insights and visualizing them in a manner that&rsquo;s both comprehensible and actionable for stakeholders.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System</title>
    <link>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/third_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 21:10:27 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Lanhsin</author>
    <guid>https://lindseyyzhang.github.io/third_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In March 2022, I studied Nakamoto&rsquo;s (2008) paper on Bitcoin during my Ethereum class. Before this, I though Bitcoin was just a way to make quick money. But after reading and learning it, I saw how special it was for the peer-to-peer transactions.
I was faced with the challenge of understanding its intricate system. But as I delved deeper, I was able to dissect and simplify these complexities piece by piece.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
